<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web design and graphic design for results-driven businesses | Athens GA</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Web design and graphic design for results-driven businesses | Athens GA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 09:59:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Websites: 01 Strategy</title>
      <link>/blog/effective-website-01-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 09:59:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/effective-website-01-strategy/</guid>
      <description>If your website isn&amp;rsquo;t selling your business, it&amp;rsquo;s likely that you launched it without a strategy. This isn&amp;rsquo;t your fault. Chances are that no one told you that you needed a strategy, they just told you that you needed a website.
You put up a website for your business because you knew that you had to have one. Everyone knows that. So, like every other business owner, you found a web designer or your next-door neighbor&amp;rsquo;s nephew (who&amp;rsquo;s really good at the internets).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Websites: 02 Content</title>
      <link>/blog/effective-website-02-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 09:59:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/effective-website-02-content/</guid>
      <description>If your website isn&amp;rsquo;t getting any traffic, it&amp;rsquo;s likely that your content stinks.
In part one we told you that your website stank because your online strategy stank. Hopefully, you sat down afterward and had a good hard think about who you are, what you offer, and why it matters.
You identified your target market and figured out where they were and how to communicate with them effectively. You found yourself a CRM and imported your customers from Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Websites: 03 Web Design</title>
      <link>/blog/effective-website-03-web-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 09:59:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/effective-website-03-web-design/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to part three in our five part series on effective business websites. We’re glad you’re here.
If you are just now joining us, here’s what you missed: We believe that most websites stink because they don’t generate business for the site owner.
In part one we told you why your online strategy stinks. In part two, we told you why your content strategy stinks.
Then you went and fixed all of that!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Websites: 04 Web Development</title>
      <link>/blog/effective-website-04-web-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 09:59:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/effective-website-04-web-development/</guid>
      <description>We started this series because we’ve found that most websites stink. They stink because they don’t generate business. We’re on a mission to fix that.
I love that you’re working on your strategy, your design, and your content, but your development stinks and it makes us sad.
Your otherwise perfect website has badly written and poorly optimized code. It’s bloated and slow and it’s hurting your user experience and SEO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Work</title>
      <link>/our-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 15:18:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/our-work/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What We Do</title>
      <link>/what-we-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 13:47:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/what-we-do/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Marketing Branch of Resolution</title>
      <link>/blog/healthcare-marketing-branch-of-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 13:35:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/healthcare-marketing-branch-of-resolution/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Cms Should You Choose</title>
      <link>/blog/which-cms-should-you-choose/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 13:32:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/which-cms-should-you-choose/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media vs Traditional Advertising</title>
      <link>/blog/social-media-vs-traditional-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 13:32:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/social-media-vs-traditional-advertising/</guid>
      <description>Our lens on all advertising and marketing efforts is pretty simple: they should generate business. &amp;#129297;
Each effort should begin with a strategy, each tactic should support that strategy, and both your strategy and tactics should have measurable goals. Each dollar spent on marketing should return in dividends. &amp;#128181;
Tracking the return on investment in traditional advertising has historically been a slow process. Outside of direct response, business would wait for the end of the quarter or the end of the fiscal year to track the results of their campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in After Effects</title>
      <link>/blog/adventures-in-after-effects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 13:27:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/adventures-in-after-effects/</guid>
      <description>We’ve had a promotional video for both branches of Resolution on our todo list for months now. We finally bit the bullet and put one together last week. It’s a rock and roll promo, so turn up your volume and hit the play button. Then check out the dirty details of how the sausage was made.
 A pencil and a notebook &amp;#128221; I’m a fan of writing things down before sitting down at a keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Thinking for Online Strategy</title>
      <link>/blog/use-design-thinking-for-online-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 12:53:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/use-design-thinking-for-online-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Design thinking is an idea whose time has come There has been a lot of talk about design thinking lately. As firm believers in user-centric design, we’re happy to see it catching on.
At its core, design thinking is a framework for problem-solving which encourages empathy and exploration.
We’re also firm believers in strategy before tactics and we’ve found design thinking to be a great framework to facilitate the formation of a thorough marketing strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How we nailed Athens SEO in 6 months</title>
      <link>/blog/athens-seo-our-six-month-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 09:23:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/athens-seo-our-six-month-results/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with on-site SEO for resolutionathens.com. We&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot and had some pretty incredible results.
Before last year, Resolution thrived as an Athens graphic design firm for nearly 25 years—solely on word of mouth and referrals.
We never had a website before mid-summer of 2016. We never advertised. For many years we operated without so much as a sign on the door. In my mind, this is the ultimate testament to Taylor’s talent as a graphic designer and the attention he gives to his clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clients</title>
      <link>/clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/clients/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission</title>
      <link>/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mission/</guid>
      <description>We are Proud to Represent Resolution We are a new firm, we are a different firm, we are a better firm. We are here because we love what we do and we enjoy a deep satisfaction by doing it well.
We are Proud of our Work No project leaves Resolution unless we would use it to represent ourselves.
We are not Pretty-Makers Our primary service is our thinking. Strategy comes first, design follows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are</title>
      <link>/who-we-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/who-we-are/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>